http://www.boneclones.com/page/privacy-and-security

info@boneclones.com
If this option is enabled, an exact search will be performed and similar words will not be searched.
Endangered Primates
Endangered Mammals (Non-primate)
Human
Primate (Non-human)
Fossil Hominid
Bird
Mammal (Non-primate)
All Human Skulls
Adult (General)
Endangered Primates
Endangered Mammals (Non-primate)
Privacy and Security
Share page:
Privacy and Security
All items sold on this website are reproductions (replicas). All Bone Clones® products are made in the USA. No real or natural bone material is available on this site.
* Effective (January 1, 2005)
We recognize and respect your need for privacy and security as you visit our site. When you visit our site to view any pages, read product information, or use our on-line calculators and tools, you do so without telling us who you are and without revealing any personal information. While we do not collect identifying information about visitors to our site, we do use standard software to collect information for the strict purpose of tracking activity on our site. This allows us to better understand how many people use our site and which pages and features are most popular. The only information we normally collect and store is:
The name of your Internet service provider.
The web site that referred you to us (if any).
The date and time the pages were accessed.
The page or pages you requested.
There are instances when you may elect to provide us with personal information. If you order one or more of our products, or send us email, you are transmitting the information. This will typically include information like your name, mailing address, email address, the items you are ordering, and any other information necessary to fulfill your order and may include credit card information. Personally identifying information that you do not enter yourself should never be transmitted. And this is always your option; this information cannot be collected unless you specifically elect to send it to us. This information is used internally only for the purpose of fulfilling your order or for contacting you directly and is not given, sold to or shared with any other organization.
When you submit personally identifying information via our online shopping cart, that information is encrypted, or scrambled, by your browser before it is transmitted back to our secure web site. This effectively prevents anyone from intercepting and reading any personal information about you. Note that this encryption does not take place if you send us email, but only when you use your web browser to order on-line.
We hope you find our website useful and informative and we are always willing to answer questions and receive suggestions. If you have either, please e-mail us at info@boneclones.com. Thank you.
* We reserve the right to change our privacy policy. A revised policy statement will only apply to data collected subsequent to its effective date. Any revisions will be posted at least 30 days prior to its effective date.
Newsletter Signup
SUBMIT >
Bone Clones, Inc. 9200 Eton Ave. Chatsworth, CA 91311 USA
800-914-0091
818-709-7991
fax: 818-709-7993
info@boneclones.com
Except where indicated otherwise, all images and text
© 1992-2020 Bone Clones, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
